

TRAINEE/JUNIOR FRONT-END **DEVELOPER**

CONTACTS



Kharkiv, Ukraine



+38(099)401-62-15



<u>denis pavlenko</u>



denispavlenko94agmail.com



denis-pavlenko

SKILLS SUMMARY

HTML&CSS(SaSS/SCSS)



Crossbrowser and responsive layout



jQuery / JavaScript





Figma/Photoshop/Avocado/Zeplin

LANGUAGES

Russian Native Ukraine Native

English Pre-Intermediate

PROFILE

I am a beginner Markup Developer with the knowledge required to the technical sphere of this direction. I already have some experience with functional.

I want to take part in a team of professionals to develop my skills and knowledge.

I am self-motivated, easy going and open to new concepts and responsibilities.

PROJECTS

Cosmetology Landing Page



<u>GitHub</u>

<u>Mountains Landing Page</u>



GitHub

WORK EXPERIENCE

Account & Project Manager at IconPartners

July 2020 - till now

in IT Svit

- Organizing and participating in negotiations with clients
- Preparing technical specifications/statements of work for the team
- Conducting weekly analyses of the legal team's reports
- Implementing quality control of the services provided
- **Account Manager**

Dec 2019 - June 2020

- Handling incoming applications and calls
- · Customer support at every stage of sales
- Lead generation

Lead administrator • Selling services and courses in Hillel IT School

Sept 2017 - Dec 2019

- Budget planning and expense reporting
- Setting up programs on computers

Administrator, leather goods store Oct 2014 - Sept 2017

• Processing of incoming applications, selling Filling site content

• Preparation and execution of documents for shipment

EDUCATION HISTORY

2014 - 2019

National Technical University "Kharkiv Polytechnic Institute"

Applied Mechanics, Master's degree

2010 - 2014

Kharkiv Mechanical Engineering College Applied Mechanics

2014 - 2015

Kharkiv Mechanical Engineering College Economist, technician with a plan

ADDITIONAL EDUCATION

• Hillel IT Shool

Course: "Front-end Basic: HTML&CSS"

Hillel IT Shool

Course: "Front-end Pro: JavaScript" (now in the process of studying)

- Big Bang! English space | Course: "English"
- Foreign Language Studio "NewTone" | "English"